I would like to DIY this wallpaper this time!
Amazing!
You must be jealous.
It's math time.
Wow!
Huh! Time stopped!
Yes, so I'm going to do some DIY right away.
Today, I'm going to ask this person to help me.
Kin.
Please help me.
Please, I'm Po-chan.
I'm Po-chan.
Please accept my regards, I'm Po-chan, Kin-chan.
Dokudoku DIY
So what should I be doing first?
First of all, I'm going to peel off as much wallpaper as I can.
Yes, thumbtacks and that kind of thing.
Let's peel it off and take it off and remove it as well
Yes, I understand.
Touching the studs reminds me of elementary school.
There was a person in charge of taking off the studs.
I was kind of helping with that.
Hmmm...
I'd like to pick them out.
Yes, how do you do it?
How does it work?
Hook it.
Oh, great.
Yes, this way, please. Wow, neat, neat.
Be careful.
Oh, great.
I say bish bish bish bish!
I got it!
Wow, it's so refreshing when it comes off.
Shall we peel it off? Yes!
Can I peel it off?
Wow, that's great!
Oh, it feels like it's flipping.
That's great.
I found one point where I can peel it off.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you want to try peeling it off there?
Oh, can I?
Yeah. - Okay.
I don't think it's going to go right through this wall.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, but, uh...
I'm gonna rip it out of someone's wall.
I'll just cut it out with my eyes.
Oh, my gosh, but...
Oh, my gosh, I've never peeled it off before.
Wow.
That's great.
Wow, that's great.
Oh, my God.
It's like the inside of a cupcake.
You know, my mom used to get mad at me when I messed up the wallpaper or peeled it off, and she said, "You can't do that.
I've heard so many people say, "No, you can't.
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
Wow, that's a lot of bb!
Maybe we can get this?
Wow, ah, ah...
huh?
Gure!
Wow!
Wow.
Wow. What's this?
Do you have it? You ever peeled a stink bug?
You must be jealous.
It's amazing how good it feels when it comes off.
It feels so good.
Wow.
Whoa. Whoa.
That's like a hide-and-seek shop.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow, that feels good.
Lately...
When I was shopping...
Don't skip the checkout line.
They passed me... while I was standing in line.
I was in line.
But I couldn't tell him.
I couldn't say I was in line.
Damn it, why didn't I tell him?
Next time I see him, I'll pass him back.
I'll never see him again.
I'm thinking of keeping both of them.
I'm thinking of taking both of them.
Wait a minute.
Where's the screw?
I got it!
Got it! I got it!
Do you do a lot of DIY?
Yes, at home.
That's great.
I've never seen you do it at home.
It's nice to have freedom.
It's fun.It's fun.
I've only done it in places where it's regulated, like rentals.
Are there places where you can rent?
There are a lot of them.
Oh, I see. You do.
There are a lot of exclusive ones.
Wow!
That's amazing. There's about as much as bath time!
Low solo and DIY!
I'll start over here and work my way down.
We'll start from here and work our way to the end, and then we'll prepare these lengths.
Yes, sir.
This length is about 2.2.
So we're going to leave a margin of about 2.4 each.
If we take 2.4 each, how many pieces can we take?
That's a lot of time.
That's about four pieces.
I'll eat six.
That was six. Six.
That's right, not four. Six.
Wow.
That's for the designer.
It's written. Wow.
Because this is 1.
At 2.4.
Two meters.
You can have it soused now.
Oh!
You can cut it with wallpaper and scissors?
That's good.
Oh, wait a minute.
Forty.
That's great.
Give me the cutter.
Yes, sir.
Oh, I need more hands.
I need to grow two more.
Great.
May I come up?
Yes, ma'am.
There's a little wrinkle here.
Here... here... here.
I can reupholster this.
Okay.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Here, lesson soup.
Here you go.
Yes, that's good.
Oh, my God.
It's too soft.
It's too soft. - Too soft.
That's what it means.
Do the whole bench.
When you make it, it's a wall.
It's a different genre.
The difficulty is
It's more subtle
I mean, it's a precious surface.
It's a shell, isn't it?
That's why it's so difficult.
But
After the wall is finished
I feel very comfortable using it.
I'll go it alone.
Wow!
Really? Isn't that fast?
You'll have to crouch down on top.
Yes, sir.
You can already see that sticking out, right?
You're doing something completely different.
Wow!
Hoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
I've got it.
I'll keep it connected.
Yes. Keep the cutter.
Good.
Ohhh, it's so hard to get down!
Wow!
Huh.
It stopped.
Mouth.
Yee-ha ha!
Wait a minute.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
Ping.
Yes, sir.
So, we're stacked this high now?
Are you sure you're okay here?
Yes, I'm fine.
Okay. - Okay.
Hey, Ping.
Oh, my God, I'm not used to this.
There's just not enough overlap.
I'm sorry.
We'll cover that up a little later.
I'll just enjoy the sound.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Logo logo DIY
Yes, so I'm done wallpapering!Yes, so I finished wallpapering!
I put up white wallpaper.
But it was so difficult to put up the wallpaper that time stopped.
I had a hard time putting it up straight.
I'm glad I was able to do it successfully.
Next, I'm going to paint!
If you like this video and think it's beautifully done
If you like this video and think it's beautifully done, please leave a like, subscribe to the channel, comment, etc.
We're looking forward to your comments! I'm looking forward to your comments!
So, goodbye!
Last but not least, I'd like to introduce a product!
Uniforms are now indispensable to prevent heat stroke
Cool Fan Vest
It has a PU coating on the back to cut ultraviolet rays
Armpits are prone to perspiration
Even with arms down
A system that allows localized wind to blow
Actually, Midori-Anzen is not only a manufacturer of safety shoes
We are the No.1 manufacturer of working uniforms.
Please check out our overview section!
Please subscribe to our channel!